# **DESTINEY MONROE**

Destiney.monroe1124@gmail.com

214-734-6406

### **OBJECTIVES**

My goal is to be a part of a company where there is growth potential for someone with my career experiences and skill set. I am highly motivated, and believe that my communication skills, commitment to excellence, and compassion for others make me and ideal candidate for a role in the healthcare industry.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **EASTFIELD COLLEGE**

**2018** Associate of Science in Healthcare Administration

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **COMERICA BANK | DALLAS, TX**

Customer Service Representative 04/2017 - Present

- Answer incoming calls
- Assist customers with account information
- · Research and adjustment
- Make outbound calls
- Account Verification

# Ace Cash Express | Mesquite, TX

Cashier 10/2016 - 04/2017

- Provided check cashing services to customers
- Opened and assigned new client accounts
- Researched and resolved billing and invoice issues
- Reconciled batch summary reports for verification and approval
- Process Loans

#### Chase Bank | Corsicana, TX

Bank Teller 5/2015 - 7/2016

- Managed customer deposits and withdrawals
- · Assist supervisors with daily retail banking customer operations
- Educate customers and resolve customer issues in everyday banking transactions

## ResCare | Corsicana, TX

#### **Healthcare Provider** 12/2013-06/2015

- Assist mentally challenge residents with everyday living activities
- Provided compassionate round the clock care for resident

#### **SKILLS**

- Understanding of confidentiality and privacy
- Great organizational skills
- Attention to detail
- Excellent computer skills
- Quickly comprehend new processes

#### **REFERENCES**

**Professional** 

**Thomas Brown** 

Comerica Bank

Team Lead

Phone: 214-986-1357

Kayla Tanner

Assistant Manager

Chase Bank

Office: 903-874-5661

Keshayla Wade

Supervisor

ResCare

Phone: 903-851-2653

#### Personal

## **Sharonda Ross**

Mesquite Tree Rehabilitation Center

Phone: 214-900-7652

Lanetia Crawford, BSN

Kindred Home Care

Phone: 254-744-5995

**Barbara Clark** 

Kindred Hospital

Phone: 469-500-6057